clixteria.com 2011-08-04

# Clixteria.com - Privacy Page

| 

** WELCOME !! ******   
Clixteria.com is a website where you get paid to click, read, signup, and do surveys online. Our site IS VERY DIFFERENT from those sites that pay you a crummy one tenth of a cent per action. We pay you top cash directly into your PayPal account for the work you do on Clixteria. We offer serious cash for those who want to work from home doing simple tasks on a computer! 

Your Clixteria membership is TOTALLY FREE! We'll povide you with your own private administration area where you can view your earnings and transfer your money directly into your PayPal account. You keep all your earnings! No fees or other BS ever! 

---  
  
** Welcome! to Clixteria.com  

### The Pay-Per-Action Website  
Where Serious Home Workers  
Earn Serious Cash

* * *

### OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Information and Use  
We do not sell, rent, or otherwise share personal information to any third parties for any reason. We respect the privacy of our users to the highest degree possible, and we are proud to say that our privacy policy is among the best of all sites on the Internet. We know that users are here because they're looking for our information, and that's the only purpose of our site.

Log Files  
Like most websites we use basic log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages and platform type. This is not personal information and cannot be linked to any individual person. This general information is used to compile help us understand more about the users of this website, to help us learn which pages users like best, and other information that help us make the site better tailored to the needs of our users in the future. THESE LOGS DO NOT REVEAL ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU!

**

 **Cookies, Email Spam, Adware, Spyware and Viruses  
We do not collect your email address and you'll never receive any spam email from us. Also, we do not place any cookies on your computer, nor do we place any spyware, adware or other intrusive programs on your computer. We are a virus-free website. We strongly believe in protecting the privacy of our users. You can feel confident in visiting our site.**

Phil  
Admin  
Clixteria.com

* * *

Copyright 2011 Clixteria.com - all rights reserved

|
